Catnip Adventures
2D Platformer

PLAYER
Horizontal movement (movement on the x-axis)
Idle-animation
Hurt-animation
- When attacked or when touching traps.
Jump
Crouch
-  Ground/Ceiling detection, etc: Player won't be able to exit the crouch state if a platform is blocking above
Melee-attack
- Inflict -1 damage per attack
Health
- Simple health system, etc 3 "lives" throughout a level

WORLD
3 different level environments
- Grassland, Snowland, Dungeon
- Unique elements to each environments (etc Icy/slippery platforms during Snowlands)
- 5 levels each, with a Boss at the end of every 5 level.
Moving platforms (horizontal movement)
Collectibles
- High-score collectibles (etc coins, fruit)
- Health-collectibles (+1 life)
Save-points
- Ability to respawn on different locations instead of respawning at the beginning of a level.
Horizontal sidescrolling
-  Camera follows Player (Cinemachine?)
- When Player moves forward (to the right), Player won't be able to return to previous locations of the level
Traps
- Static inanimate objects
- Inflicts -1 damage to Player On Collision

Enemies
Static enemy
- No horizontal movement
- Inflicts -1 damage On Collision
Simple Moving enemy
- Simple horizontal movement
- Inflicts -1 damage On Collision
Projectile Enemy/Attack Enemy
- Horizontal movement 
- Follows Player when Player enters it's range
- Will attack through shooting projectiles towards the Player when in range
- Inflics -1 damage On Collision
- Projectile inflicts -1 damage 


